(Sheldon:)I'm sensing things
have gotten awkward.
(Amy:)No. It's okay.
(Amy:)If we're friends, we should be
able to talk about anything.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Amy:)So, you had some questions
about me seeing other people.
(Sheldon:)Just a few.
(Amy:)Go ahead.
(Sheldon:)How many dates have you been on?
(Sheldon:)Who were they with?
Where'd you go?
(Sheldon:)Where did you meet them?
Did you sleep with them?
(Sheldon:)And how much longer
to the aquarium?
(Sheldon:)I'm getting kind of hungry.
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
(Amy:)I have been on six dates
with three different people.
(Amy:)It was either for
coffee or dinner.
(Amy:)One I met at a bookstore
and two I met online.
(Amy:)I haven't slept with anyone.
(Amy:)The aquarium is
40 minutes away.
(Amy:)And there's a baggie of Cheerios
for you
(Amy:)in the glove compartment.
Uh, regular or honey nut?
(Amy:)I mixed them.